psip.me 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy - psip.me

Psip.me is committed to protecting the privacy interests of its customers, end users, distributors and suppliers. This privacy policy is intended to provide you with general information on how Frymyip.com collects, uses, stores, and shares information.

All data processed through this site is controlled by Psip.me ([info@psip.me](mailto:info@psip.me)).

## What data is collected and by who?

### Advertising Networks:

Third-party vendors, including Google, use technology such as cookies and web beacons to serve ads based on your usage data. Any information collected through this process is handled under the terms of our advertising partners' privacy policies. 

You can read our Cookie Policy here: [Cookie Policy](https://psip.me/cookies)

You can opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising here (<https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated>)

### Google Analytics:

We use Google Analytics to collect information about usage. The information collected by Google Analytics will only be used for statistical analysis related to your browsing behaviour on this specific site. The information we obtain from Google Analytics is not personally identifying, nor is it combined with information from other sources to create personally identifying information.

Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit the site, but this cookie cannot be used by anyone except Google, and the data collected cannot be altered or retrieved by services from other domains.

Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Service (<https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html>) and the Google Privacy Policy (<https://www.google.com/policies/privacy>).

You may choose to opt out by turning off cookies in the preferences settings in your web browser. You can also visit Google’s Opt Out Tool (<http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>)

## How is the collected data used?

Psip.me aggregates all coarse data and does not store any personally identifiable information. The aggregated data is used to measure traffic to the website, time spent on the website, and activities taken while on the website, including engagements with advertising. For more information about how data is collected and used, please view our [Cookie Policy](https://frymyip.com/cookies).

## What else do I need to know?

### Links to Other Websites:

Psip.me may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we have no control over any other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites, and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
